Dubofsky, Melvyn Papers 6218
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Miscellaneous conference papers (Box 10)
  - FA Warren Queens College Lecture on IWW Oct, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - OAA Paper on IWW (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - MUHA - Labor History - Paper and Comments, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - RIC - High School Symposium, 1873-1897 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Lecture Economic Development in Backwards Area (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Peace Corps Lectures on Socialism and Amer. Labor (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - High School Talk on Impact of Industrialization (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - TLL + the Labor Upheaval of 1930s (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Past, Present, + Future of Work, Richland Teachers Assn. (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - J. Jacobson - S Pessay (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Ereming Press "Right To Work" (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Labor Leaders (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - General Theories of Society (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Wallerstein - Hopkins, Structured Transformation (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - E + BF Genovese: Politics of Social History, JSH (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - T Judt Social History and Historians History wkshp J. (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Mary Ryan Marie Modern Women, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - M Holler: Organized Annie in Chicago (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Analysis of Progressive Movement (Filene) (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - U Greene, The Role of Ethnic Leaders (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - S Engerman: US - BWI Slave Demography (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Bluestone: Genovese and Marxism (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - J Lemisch - Boston Massacre and H Zolel (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - J Henretta, Families + Farms W and MQ (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - R Wiele, Social Functions of Public Education, AQ (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - S Troen, Educ. Reform, Adolescence, + Economics (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - RR Street, Calif. Ag. At Turn of Century (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - P Forcey: No Waves: Time C's of America Reform (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - S Wank - Euro. Diplo. History Essays (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - G Stern, Hitler's Social Revolution (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Family History - A Skolneck JIH (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - C Lasch: Role of Intellectuals (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Ads for NYC Labor Bank _ District (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Immigration History Newsletter (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Coal Miners Project and So. Labor History Assn. (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - NA: Census + Other Data Guides (Box 10, Folder 60)
  - J. Lenlicke Dealing Out Capital (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Arbitration Press (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - R Mesmalano, Papers on Govt. Regression of Radicals (Box 10, Folder 63)
- Publications, unpublished articles and papers by a variety of scholars with Melvyn Dubofsky's comments (Box 11)
  - Dubofsky Articles (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Stanley Group World Labor Division Papers (J. Henrich) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - David Gordon: Historical Dynamics of Capitalist Accumulation - Model (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Anarchism + Reductionism (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - S M Lasky S + S Essay on Class Theory (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Lee Benson, "Marx's Theories of Social Conflict" (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bill Lazonick - URPE - Capital to Labor (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Notes on English Industrial Rev. Thompson on Time (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - English Labor History Habsban + Pelling (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Erik Wright "Class Boundaries in Advanced Capitalist Societies NLR (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - M Tranti, "Workers + Capital" Teles (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - C Castoriadis "History of Workers Movements" (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - M Shepherd + RE Concept of a Labor Aristocracy (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - F Freedeman, "Internal Structure of America Proletariat" SR (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - A Kesslor - Harris "Women and Work, 1870-1930 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - G Kolbo, "Working Wares" (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - BD palmer, "Historiography Canadian WC History" (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - James E Crown, Paper on Theories of Strikes (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - EJ Habshann - New Unionism and Syndicalism in GB (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - M Sheffty "Labour Lift and the Strike Against War." (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Gulick and Bers, on Perlman vs. Theory, ILR (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Kreuger - Amer. Labor Historiography (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Papers: Class and Class Con (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - J Green "American Radical Historians" P+P (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Rodgers "Tradition Modernity and Amer. Indus. Worker" (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - MJ Cassidy "Southern Workers and Social Change" (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - G Nash Poor in Franklin's Philadelphia (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Berthoff: Social Order of Anthracite Region (Box 11, Folder 28)
    1825-1902
  - S. Thornstrom: Working - Class (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Guffen: Social Mobility in Poughkeepsie (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - C Griffen: Occupational Mobility 19th C (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - DJ Walkowitz, Workering - Class Women in Cohoes (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - H. gutman - Paper on Discontinuity in American Labor History and Materials on Social structure in Paterson (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - D. Montgomery: Shuttle + Cross, Kensington Riot (Box 11, Folder 34)
    1844
  - C. Stephenson Social Mobility and the free Labor Ideology (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - A Dawley and P. Foler - WC Culture and Politics, 1820-1890 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - E Glassberg, " Ethnicity and Poverty in Pluck, 1880" - PA History (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Working - Class Saloon and Culture (Kingsberg) (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - P Taft: Origins of Business Unionism (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - KA Harrey, Maryland Eval. Miners, 1835-1910 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Ch. Madison "William H Sylvis" (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - D. McMurray "Burlington RR Labor Policy" (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Miners in West, VA: Ethnicity, Race, and Reclusion (K. Bawley + D. Corbin) (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - V Greene, Slaves, Strikes and Unions, Pa, 1897 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - M Dubofsky, IITLM (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Ethnicity. Immigrants and US Labor History (Korman, G) (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - AJ Lane, Molly Maguires (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - M Dubofsky TPOSIT (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - M Dubofsky RFTGOT (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - HV Browne "Ponderly and Church Labor Relations" (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - TJ Condor, NYC Election of 1886 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Stereo J. Ross, "Amer. Workers and May Day Strikes of 1886" (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - IWA + Appeal to Anarchists 1883 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Chi. Labor Movement and Life of Albert Parsons (Box 11, Folder 54)
  - 19th C political Reformer - Ethnic - Religious and Class - PSQ Essays (McCormick + Wyman) (Box 11, Folder 55)
  - Chafe: Negro and Populism in Kansas (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Goodwyn, "Populism in East Texas" (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - M Dubofsky APPATR (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - Unions + Populist Party (Peterson) (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - D Montgomery "Strikes in 19th C America" SSH (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - K Stone, "Job Structure in Steel Industry" (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - J Amsden + S Brier "Coal Mariners on Strike" (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - M Dubfosky GATIOR (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - Gompers, Japan, 1913 (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - UMW - Black - White Relations (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - WFM Poetry, 1903-1905 (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - J Laslett: British + US Eval Miners + Politics (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - Laslett, Hodge, Wolfle Coal Miners and third - Party Politics in Ill, 1880-1924 (Box 11, Folder 68)
  - M. Stern "Black Strikebreakers" and Wash St., 1891 (Box 11, Folder 69)
  - W. G. Whittaker: Gompers and Imperialism (Box 11, Folder 70)
  - J.T. Cumbler, "Shoe Workers in 20th C Lynn" (Box 11, Folder 71)
  - Rogin - Volunteerism (Box 11, Folder 72)
  - Tom White, "RR Workers in the Pacific NW, 1895-1916" (Box 11, Folder 73)
  - C. Schnates, "Struggle v. AFL Hegemony" PNQ (Box 11, Folder 74)
  - Paul French, "Original Labor in butte, 1878-1896" (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - D. Bercuson - "Labour Radicalism and the Western Industrial Frontier: 1897-1919' (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - J. Conin: Western Miner Radicalism (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - JC Faster, "Life and Death in Western Mines, 1900-1930" (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - J Conlin, IWW and SPA (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - B Palmer and C Heron, "Industrial Conflict in So. Ontario," CHR (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - NJ Words, "Industrial Relation Policies of America Mgt, 1900-1933" (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - D Nelson, "Taylorism at Bethlehem" (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - J Mond and J Hinton NLR Workers Control (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - D. Montgomery, LH and JSH Essays on Workers' Control (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - H Shapiro, "The McNamara Case" (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - R Asher, Workmen's Comp. Essay (Box 11, Folder 86)
  - B Johnpull - De Leon (Box 11, Folder 87)
  - J Laslett - Paper on Socialism + America Labor movement (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - AR McCormack, "Wallies + Blankstiffs, IWW in Western Canada" (Box 11, Folder 89)
  - RE Snyder, "IWW in Little Falls, NY" (Box 11, Folder 90)
  - R Snyder, IWW in Little Falls, (Women) (Box 11, Folder 91)
  - Ann Schufield, "IWW + Women" (Box 11, Folder 92)
  - TW Smith "The Muckrakers and the Wobblies" (Box 11, Folder 93)
  - J Green: Working - Class Radicalism in La. + Texas (Box 11, Folder 94)
  - J R Green - Coal Miners + Socialism in the Southwest (Box 11, Folder 95)
  - D Bercuson, "IWW and OBU" (Box 11, Folder 96)
  - S M Lipset, Way No Socialism in NJ Commerce (Box 11, Folder 97)
  - JHM Laslett, "Reflections on Failure of Socialism" (Box 11, Folder 98)
  - J Cohert ACLS Proposal and Article on Butte, 1914-1917 (Box 11, Folder 99)
  - C Leinenweber: NYC Students in the Streets - S and S (Box 11, Folder 100)
  - Sally Miller, "T Malkiel" AJHSQ (Box 11, Folder 101)
  - N Basen: K R Ohare (Box 11, Folder 102)
- Publications, unpublished articles and papers by a variety of scholars with Melvyn Dubofsky's comments (continued) (Box 12)
  - N Basen, RR O'Hare Essay (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - N Basen, Jennie Higginses Essay (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - B D Palmer, Decline of IWW (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - J Grabelsky "IBEW Split and PCHE Strike, 1908-1913" (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - MC Roddick: Hutchinson and Carpenters (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Russian Jew in Baltimore Clothing Industry, 1900-1920 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - R Asher, Jewish Unions and AFL 1903-1935 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - W J Breen, "Black Women and WWI" (South) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - J Johnson "W Wilson and Eval, WWI," Prologue (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - R Asher, Paper - Memories of 1919 Steel Strike (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - D Long, Tampa Cigar-Union Struggle, 1919-1921 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Coal Miners, UMW, Iowa (1920), and New Deal (Johnson-Johnson Straw) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - R Zieger, Republicans and Labor 1919-1929 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - S Fraser, Hillman, ACW, and RAIC (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - H Hoover + Soft Coal (E Hawley) (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Coal Miners' Wages - Records 1929-1933 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Chas. Howlett, "Brookward Labor college" Mid-America (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - E Hawley Essays on corporate Inclusion (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - M Rishin "From Gompers to Hillman" (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - M Johnson: The Anti-Injunction Movement (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Glenn Seretan "Social Banditry in Depression America" (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Lynds - Middleton Muncie 1925-1935 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Verba, S Class Consciousness (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Sternsker, B Victims of the Great Depression, Self-Blame (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Sternsker, B Great Depression Labor (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - D Brody "Emergence of Mass Production Unionism" (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Peter Fruedlander - Midland Steel Oral History + Research Proposal Papers (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - S Lynd, "Crowd, Rank and File, and Party in CIO" (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - OAH Program Rubber and Auto Workers, 1933-1946 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - N Lichtenstein, Auto Workers in WWII (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Steve Frazer, ACWA + Origins of New Deal (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Ron Schatz " Union Pioneers at GE and Westshore 1933-1937 JAH (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - R Street, Paul Taylor Essay (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - W J Stern: California (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Workers + the Great Depression (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - TT Spencer :LNPL and 1936 Election in PA" PA History (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - J Green and S Lynd, Labor in 1930's RA (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - S Vitto Mss: New Deal Labor Policy (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - R Radesh: Corporate Ideology of Labor Leaders (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - R H Zieger, Rev. of WC Autolines - Md. History (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - R Boryezka " Military + Factionalism in UAW, 1937-1941" (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - J L Baughman "Closses + Company Towns - Little Steel Strike" (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - M Gordon, CR and Labor in 1930s SR (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - R Keeran, CP and Auto workers Book Intro (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - R Cuff "Military - Industrial Complex" (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - James + James: Trotskyites and Teamsters (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - R Schatz, Labor + Mgt. in 20C US, GE and Westinghouse (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - R Keeran "Communist in Autos, WWII" Sci. + Society (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Sitkoff: Detroit Race Riot 1943 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - C Mauer, Post WWII US Foreign Econ Policy (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - CIO + Communism: 1940-1948 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Prickett: Communism + the CIO (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - JR Prickett: communism and Factionalism, UAW, 1939-1947 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - AFL D Dubinsky, Communism and Politics, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Unions + corruption (Hutchinson) (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Reuther + the UAW (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Lynd - Klare - MD - Kennedy - Papers and comments - Labor Law (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - K Klare, "Labor Law on Ideology" Mss. (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Sol Barkins "Roads to Expansion" Cross (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - B B Seligman: Automation and The State (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Tom Kahn: Economics of Equality (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Sexton: Middle-Class Workers and Politics (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Sexton: John L Lewis (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - J Weinstein "Left: OED New" - SR (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - J Geschwender League of Revo Black Workers (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - T Kreuger, "Labor in Con - Temporary America," JSH (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Miscellaneous - Roger Baldwin and Politics + Revolution (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - R Schatz, Marense and US Workers (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - A. Syzmanski, "Trends in American Class Structure" (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - TU Misc. (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - TammentL Daniel Bill Socialist Collection (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - M Alnamontz and PA David (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - NYT, Contemporary Demo and Trends (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - J Petras; Sociology of Development and Exploitation (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - FBC Seminar Papers (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - FBC Seminar Papers (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - Manchester, NH Industrial Archaeology (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - Bilbo: UFWA (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Paul Jacobs: Collective Bargaining (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - A A Blum " Collective Bargaining Ritual on Realty" (Box 12, Folder 78)
  - Misc. The Cross of Labor and Collec. Bargaining, 1960s (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - B B Seligman "Balance Sheet of America Unions (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - T. R. Brooks: Black Upsurge in Unions (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - C. Chravez and Farm Workers (J. G. Dunne) (Box 12, Folder 82)
  - Essay + Articles on TV Growth - Patterns + Cycles (Box 12, Folder 83)
- Book reviews by Melvyn Dubofsky, drafts, research files (Box 13)
  - Book Revs. 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Book Revs. - Misc. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - P Foner: Rev. Essay and J R C Notes (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Rev.: Kung and Dutton, "Preston Strike, 1853-1854," J. Econ. History (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - AHR N Salvatore Review (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - PHR + Chi. Hist: Book Res. (Kern, Frank + Walkowitz) (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - LH: A Kraditor Rev, Radical Persuasion (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - J. W. Byrkt Rev. (Arizona Labor) NMHR (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Rev.: J. R. Conlin, At Point of Prediction, ITT (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Rev. P. Taft, Organizing Dixie, AHR (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Rev. R. Steinberg, Wage + Harris, Labour P L T (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Rev. G. S. Kealey, Toronto Workers, QC (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Review: "The Wobblies," for LH (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Rev. E. Shuls, Industrial Peacemaker, AHR (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Book Revs. - C Schwantes Radical Heritage, ILWCH (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - RAH Rev. Essay: Montgomery and Brody (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Rev. J. Festschrift (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Brockport L H Conference, March 14, 1980 D Montgomery Rev. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Rev. S Fine, F Murphy New Deal Years (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - RAH: Katzman + Hamburger on Domestic Senate (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - JAH Review: Ideas of Organized Labor (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Rev. of Rodgers + Gilbert "Adam in curse," RAH (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - BHR: Dubinsky - Raskin Rev. (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - AHR Rev.: Meister + Luftis, Farm Worker (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Rev.: I Yellowitz, Industrialization and Amer. Labor Movement, ILR (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Rev: Kealey + Warrian, eds., Canadian W. C. History, JAH (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Rev. R Krukins, Pursuing the American Dream (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - R Krickens LH Exchange (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - H Gutman, Work, Society, Culture Rev: Rev. in Amer. History (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Rev. F Marquart, UAW Ill Hist Journal (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - AHR Review (Reuthers) and OAH Review (W Grailmer) (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Review: E. H. Monkkonen, "Dangerous Class" for LH (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Review: F. Russell A City in Tenor (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - JAH Review: McNaught and Bercuson, Winnipeg Gerund Strike (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - OAH Review of R. Lingenfelters Hardrock Miners (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Book Rev.: S Miller, Berger and Socialism - Heldruf Pub. Reviews (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Review: Stein, California and Dust Bowl (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Review: Ellison, Support for Secession, Reviews in History (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Goulder - Meany Review- New Politics (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Review: J. E. Finley, UMW (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Review: W.M. Dick: Labor, CHR (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Review: Wyncham Mortimer, Organize (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Review AHR: Grulls, Struggle for Labor Loyalty (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Lennett Review (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - DeCoux Review - Progressive (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - MR - Radesh Review (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - JF Wall - Carnegie Review (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - MR - P Buhle, WSBA Exchange (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Scolett Mss. (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Review of Eggert for Ill Journal (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Ozanne Review - Monthly Labor Review (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - AHR Review (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Montgomery Review - Wisconsin History Mag. (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Bisno Review (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - foner - IWW Review (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - G. Adams Book Review (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Conlin - Wienstein Review (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - A. Simons Review (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Nation: Bernstein - Fine Reviews (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Review: Vito Marcantonio (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - WSBA, Jensen and LH Review (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Joe Hill Review: NY Times (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - book Reviews (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Jewish Labor Leader B. Schlesinger (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - McGraw-Hill Encyclopedia: Bios of American Labor Leaders (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Ency. World Bio. Sketches (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - IWW - Encyclopedia American (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - DAH - IWW Article (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Revised Preface: WSBA (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - DSOC Corres: Labor Day Article on Socialism + Labor (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Cornell U. Exec. Article: U.S. Labor Movement Service 1930s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Case Western Reserve Bicentennial (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - A Weinstein - VOA Homestead - Essay (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - WEH - Eckhart, 2nd. - JLL Essay (Box 13, Folder 74)
- Course material, exams, lecture notes, miscellaneous (Box 14)
  - AJH: Rischin Commentary (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - The Nation - IWW Essay (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Greenwood Reprints (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Socialism Essay: Emerge of American Political history (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Dictionary of American Economic History Essay on Labor Organizations (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Intro: for LH Documents for RH - 4 Vols. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Misc., Coal Miners, Retirement Plan (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - History 356 - Legal History Spring 1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - History 380V - Fall 1993 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - History 540E - spring 1994 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Hist. 380V - Soc. and Culture US Since 1945 (Fall 1991) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Modern Amer. Civ. Lectures (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - History 104 Spring 1984 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - History 104 - spring 91 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - History 104 - spring 1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - History 257 0 Fall 1994 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - History 257 - Spring 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - History 601 M - Fall 1993 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - History 501D Fall 1990 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - History 520B Dubofsky (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - History 601C - Fall 1989 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - History 501E - Comparative WC history, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    spring
  - History 533A, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Fall
  - History 533A, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - History 331G Houlihan (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - History 331C Dubofsky (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - History 533A, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - History 533A, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    Spring
  - History 533F Dubofsky (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - History 533A Dubofsky (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - History 332B Dubofsky (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - History 601: Research Seminar, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - History 401C, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - US History to 1865 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - U Since 1865 - Syllabi (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - History 104 Dubofsky (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - History 221 Notes (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Lectures: Black History Since 1865 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Carmichael and Clearer on Black Power in London times (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Lectures: Economic Change, 1865-1914 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Lectures: The City + the Immigrants (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Women in US History 1877-1920 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Lectures: Farmers and Workers in an Industrial Society (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Lectures: Politics, 1865-1890 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Lectures: Populism to Progressivism (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Lectures on the 1920s (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Lectures: The New Deal (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Lecture: The Tech Society (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Lectures: American Imperialism (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Lectures: America and World War (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Lectures: Cold War and Counter - Revolution (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - History 104: Upheaval of the 1960s (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Discussion Questions for History 151 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - British Press on Vietnam, Cambridge, and Kent State (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Louis Heren on American Liberalism and His Critics (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Louis Heren on Violence in US (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - History 174, Spring, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - History 254 Spring, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 58)
- Course material, exams (continued). Drafts of articles, early correspondence. (Box 15)
  - US 1877-1917 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - J Garrety: Bio. Dict. Mother Jones (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - History 734: Topics in Gilded Age (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - History 321 C Dubofsky (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - History 331C, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Amer. Eco. History to 1877 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Amer. Eco. History Since 1877 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Urban History Course Items (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - History 298T, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - History 284, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Amer. Labor History From 1987 Sillabi (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - History 401C, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Ethnic Life, Clippings (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Crime, Police and Law Enforcement Clippings (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - History and Theory Seminar (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - T Hopkins: Soc. Theory Reading Lists (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - State and Economic (Box 15, Folder 16)